Speaker: Miriam really liked her job – it was very interesting.
I worked from home, so I was with the children a lot and I loved it. In general life was good.
It was quite cheap – cheaper than in the UK.
We joined a sports club, where the children learned to swim, and I played a lot of tennis, one of my favourite sports.
The people in Durham were very friendly.
They often invited us to their homes.
It was easy to meet people at the sports club, or at the university where Miriam worked.
And there were so many new places to see!
At weekends we visited some of the beautiful national parks.
They were very different from English parks!
In one park there was a sign saying Don’t disturb the snakes – Sacha loved it!
I also remember a trip to a country music festival at a blueberry farm.
It was fantastic.
First we listened to the music, and then we picked a lot of blueberries – they’re Elena’s favourite fruit.
But after that trip she didn't want to eat a blueberry for at least two weeks!
We stayed in Durham for a year. After that we returned to England, because my wife’s job finished.
But we loved our life in the USA, and we're thinking of going back there in maybe two or three years.